Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1104, Operators and Service Employees; Records apap121
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Membership Files - [RESTRICTED], 1975-2001 (Bulk 1983-1999); Undated; 6; 5.8 cubic ft.
  - National Labor Relations Board Grievances, 1984-2001; 6.3
    - Civil Action #CIV-86-0563, Unfair Labor Practice, 1986 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
    - Civil Action #84-0139, J. Alessi and R. Sebulski, 1984 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
    - Civil Action #86-CV-476, Brock vs. Telephone Traffic Union Upstate, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
    - Civil Action #86-CV-476, C.A. Lesniowski, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
    - Civil Action #86-CV-476, E. Kopycinski, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
    - Civil Action #86-CV-476, M.J. Ferrentino, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
    - Civil Action #86-CV-476, M. Krueger, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
    - Civil Action #86-CV-476, S. McFarland, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
    - Civil Action #86-CV-476, R. Marrara, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
    - Disaffiliation-Specifically Alessi and Sebulski vs. Telephone Traffic Union, 1984 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Failure to Provide Requested Information, 1997; 1999 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - General Case Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - General Grievance Correspondence, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - General Grievance Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Grievance #1310 and 1313, Poppenberg and Bell, et. al., 1996-1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Grievance #1402, S. Moore, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Grievance #1495, B. Kriegbaum, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Grievance #9311, G. Seminaro, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Grievance #9375, A. Crisp, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Grievance #9414-9415, R. Parker, et. al., 1996 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Grievance #9427, L. Carpenter, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Grievance #9432, R. Garrett, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Grievance #9433, M.A. Johnson, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Grievance #9435, M. Barker, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Grievance # 9439, A. Lipari, 1997 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Grievance #9460, J. Stamatakis, 1997 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Higher Tax Rate During Strike, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Labor Department Investigation, 1984-1986 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Medical Expense Plan--Litigation Against NYNEX, 1989 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5-6)
    - New York Telephone Co. vs. CWA, et. al., 1989 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Pending Board Charges, 1997-1999 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Selection of Hours / Unfair Labor Practice, 1989; 1992 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Unfair Labor Practice (ULP) Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Unfair Labor Practice (ULP) Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Winback Program, 1992 (Box 4 (6-Membership Files - [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
- Memorabilia, 1989; 1991; Undated; 7; 0.3 cubic ft.
  Arranged by format.
  This series contains a variety of artifacts from the TTUU's history, including buttons, bumper stickers, and banners. At least one banner is strike-related, dated 1989, while another is related to AT&T's replacement of live operators with voice-recorded menu options. There are also two hats, a fly swatter with a caption regarding the bugging of phone lines, and a recording of scab messages from a CWA officer's answering machine.
  - Bumper Stickers, Undated (Box 1 (7-Memorabilia), Item 1)
  - Buttons, Undated (Box 1 (7-Memorabilia), Item 2)
  - Scab messages left on CWA officer's answering machine, Undated (Cassette 1)
  - Fly swatter, Undated (Box 1 (7-Memorabilia), Item 3)
  - Hats, Undated (Box 1 (7-Memorabilia), Item 4)
  - "CWA Local 1112"" Banner, Undated (Map-tube 1)